toystory
toystory
Money, money, money. Hey!
!پول، پول، پول
You got a date with justice, one-Eyed Bart.
تو بايد به دست عدالت سپرده بشي !بارت" يك چشم"
Too bad, Sheriff. I 'm a married man.
.خيلي بد شد كلانتر.من يه مرد متاهلم
One-Eyed Betty!
!بتي" يه چشم"
I think you dropped something, mister.
.فكر كنم يه چيزي رو انداختين، آقا
- Jessie? - Give it up, Bart!
!جسي - !تسليم شو، بارت -
You've reached the end of the line!
!شما به آخر خط رسيدين
I always wanted to go out with a bang!
هميشه دوست داشتم!با يه انفجار بزرگ كارم رو تموم كنم
- Oh, no! - The orphans!
!اوه، نه - بچه يتيم‌ها -
Hate to leave early, but our ride is here.
نميخوام به اين زودي برم .ولي ماشينم اومده دنبالم
It's me or the kiddies, Sheriff. Take your pick.
.گرفتن من يا نجات بچه‌ها .تصميم بگير، كلانتر
Ride like the wind, Bullseye!
"مثل باد بتاز، "بولزاي
Hold him steady!
!برو نزديكش
Woody, hurry!
!وودي"، عجله كن"
No!
!نه
Glad I could catch the train!
!من ميتونم يه قطار رو بگيرم
Now let's catch some criminals.
.بيا رد چند تا مجرم رو بگيريم
To infinity and beyond!
!تا بي‌نهايت و فراتر از اون
Reach for the sky.
برو به آسمون
You can't touch me, Sheriff!
!تو دستت به من نميرسه، كلانتر
I brought my attack dog with a built-in force field.
من سگ وحشي‌ام رو ميارم با قدرت حفاظتي‌اش
Well, I brought my dinosaur who eats force-field dogs.
من هم دايناسورم رو ميارم كه سگ تو رو ميخوره
Evil Dr. Pork Chop!
!دكتر خوكي شيطان صفت
That's Mr. Evil Dr. Pork Chop to you.
آقاي دكتر خوكي شيطان صفت!در خدمت شماست
"Buzz, shoot your laser at my badge."
!باز، ليزرت رو به سمت نشان من بگير
"Woody, no. It'll kill you." "Just do it!"
!ولي اينكار تو رو ميكشه -!هر كاري كه ميگم، بكن -
"You're going to jail, Bart." "Watch out!"
تو به زندان ميري بارت - !مراقب باش -
Mom!
!مامان
No, no, no. Just keep playing.Just pretend I 'm not here.
نه، نه، ادامه بده. انگار من اينجا نيستم
Oh,no, Molly!
!اوه،نه، "مالي
No, it's okay, Mom. It's a fifty-foot baby from outer space.
.مهم نيست مامان اون یه آدم فضاییه پونزده متریه.
And she's on a rampage. Run for your lives!
كه ديوونه شده !فرار كنين! جونتون رو نجات بدين
Buster, get out of there. Does the red light mean it's going?
از اونجا بیا بیرون. چراغ قرمز يعني داره فيلم ميگيره؟
Come on. Say "Happy birthday" to Molly.
"يالا، بگو تولدت مبارك "مالي
- Happy birthday! - Charming.
تولدت مبارك - عزيزم -
Happy birthday!
تولدت مبارك
- Look how tall you're getting. - Yeah!
نگاه كن چقدر قدت بلند شده آره
"I came as fast as I could. Buzz, behind you!"
با تمام سرعت اومدم - !باز، پشت سرت -
"Got it, Woody."
.دارمش، وودي
Buzz Lightyear to the rescue!
!باز لايت ير"، براي نجات شما اومده"
"Good work, Buzz."
كارت عالي بود، باز
Okay, places, everyone. Come on, come on. Get in position.
بسيار خب همگي آماده باشين همه در موقعيت
Wait! I can't find my other eye.
.صبر كنين. نميتونم اون يكي چشمم رو پيدا كنم
- All right, whose foot's in my face? - It's mine. Give it back.
پاي كيه روي صورت من؟ - !مال منه! پسش بده -
You have saved our lives. We are eternally grateful.
تو جون ما رو نجات دادي و ما تا ابد ازت متشكريم
Buzz! Mind if I squeeze in next to ya?
باز اشكالي نداره كنار تو بشينم؟
Yes. No. I mean, why would I mind squeezing next to you?
آره... نه... چه اهميتي داره؟
Is it hot in here?
هواي اينجا گرمه؟
Here they come!
!دارن ميان
Sarge, you got it?
گروهبان، آورديش؟
Mission accomplished.
!ماموريت انجام شد
Hooray!
!عاليه
Careful. Careful!
!مراقب باشين!مراقب باشين
All right, guys. We got one shot at this. Everyone ready?
.بسيار خب بچه‌ها، فقط همين يه فرصت رو داريم همه آمادن؟
We're ready, Woody. Let's do it!
!آماده‌ايم! بياين انجامش بديم
Okay, Buzz. Make the call.
بسيار خب باز. تماس بگير
Target is on approach.
.هدف نزديك ميشه
Just like we rehearsed it, guys.
.همونطور كه تمرين كرده بوديم، بچه‌ها
Hello?
الو؟
Hello? Anyone there?
الو؟كيه؟
Molly, stay out of my room!
.مالي، به اتاق من كاري نداشته باش
I wasn't in your room.
.من كه به اتاقت نيومدم
Then who was messing with my stuff?
پس كي رفته سراغ وسايل من؟
It wasn't me.
.من نبودم
Well, that went well.
.خب، خوب پيش رفت
He held me! He actually held me!
اون منو گرفت !اون واقعا منو گرفت
This is just sad.
.خيلي ناراحت كنندست
Who we kiddin'? The kid 's seventeen years old.
كي رو داريم گول ميزنيم؟ .اون بچه الان هفده سالشه
We ain't ever gettin' played with.
.ديگه با ما بازي نميكنه
Guys, hey, hold up.
.هي بچه‌ها صبر كنين
We need a staff meeting. Everyone! A staff meeting!
ما بايد يه جلسه بذاريم !همه جلسه داريم
Not again!
!دوباره نه
Come on. Slink, gather everyone up.
يالا "اسلينكي"، همه رو جمع كن
We are gathered, Woody.
"ما همه جمعيم، "وودي
Okay. First off,
... خب. اول از همه
we all knew operation Playtime was a long shot.
همه ميدونيم كه عمليات بازي‌مون شكست خورد
More like a misfire.
.خب تيرمون به سنگ خورد
But we've always said this job isn't about getting played with. It's about...
ولي گفتم كه اين كار براي بازي نيست ... بلكه براي
Being there for Andy. We know.
!با "اندي" بودنه. همه ميدونيم
But we can try again! Right?
.ما دوباره ميتونيم امتحان كنيم مگه نه؟
I 'm callin' it, guys. We're closing up shop.
بچه‌ها من دارم ميگم .ديگه شانسي نداريم
What?
چي؟
Andy's going to college any day now. That was our last shot.
.اندي" تا چند روز ديگه ميره كالج" .اين آخرين فرصت ما بود
We're going into attic mode, folks.
بايد به وضعيت رفتن به .اتاق زيرشيرووني بريم، بچه‌ها
Keep your accessories with you at all times.
.همه‌ي وسايلتون هميشه همراهتون باشه
Spare parts, batteries, anything you need for an orderly transition.
باتري، قطعات يدكي، هر چيزي كه براي نقل مكان موقت نياز دارين
Orderly? Don't you get it? We're done! Finished! Over the hill!
موقت؟ چي داري ميگي !ما كارمون ساختست. تموم شد
Hey, hey, hey, now. Come on, guys. We all knew this day was coming.
هي، هي، هي .همه‌ي ما ميدونستيم چنين روزي ميرسه
Yeah, but now it's here.
.آره، اما حالا كه رسيده
Look, every toy goes through this. No one wants to see...
هر اسباب‌بازي‌اي به اين مرحله ميرسه ... هيچكسي نميخواد
Hey, Sarge! What are you doing?
هي، گروهبان، چيكار ميكني؟
War's over, folks.Me and the boys are moving on.
.جنگ ديگه تموم شد. من و افرادم داريم ميريم
- Moving on? - You're going AWoL?
ميرين؟ - دارين از خدمت فرار ميكنين؟
We done our duty. Andy's grown up.
.ما وظيفه‌مون رو انجام داديم.اندي ديگه بزرگ شده
And let's face it,when the trash bags come out,
...بايد با حقيقت روبرو شد. وقتي كيسه زباله بياد
we army guys are the first to go.
.اول از همه ما سربازها رو توش ميندازن
- Trash bags? - Who said anything about trash bags?
كيسه‌ي زباله؟ - كي درباره كيسه زباله حرفي زده؟ -
It has been an honor serving with you. Good luck, folks.
.خدمت به شما باعث افتخار ما بود .موفق باشين، رفقا